Sir Tokito…
Don't ever underestimate me,
you little brat.
DEMON SLAYER: SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
EPISODE 9:
MIST HASHIRA MUICHIRO TOKITO
No, I'm not underestimating you.
I'm just stating a fact.
You're gonna die from me
cutting off your head in any case.
Because right now,
I feel like I'm in good shape.
I wonder why.
That right there! You're underestimating
me from your tone, you brat!
You've hardly been alive
more than 10 years.
That being said, there's not a single
thing about you I can respect.
The way you look and the way you talk
are disgusting.
You're just too uncultured and poor
to understand
my beauty, grace, and elegance.
Like showing a book
to an illiterate latrine bug!
You're the one who looks like
he lives in a chamber pot.
Shut up, you latrine bug!
That blade is as short as your limbs.
It can't reach my neck.
No. It definitely did a minute ago.
And anyway, your limbs are shorter.
Oh, were you talking to yourself?
Sorry for interrupting.
What a cheap provocation.
Did you think I, Gyokko,
would be upset by that?
You seem desperate to win. It's unsightly.
UPPER
FIVE
What's wrong?
I was just wondering.
Is that vase distorted in shape?
It doesn't look symmetrical.
What poor workmanship.
That's because your eyeballs are rotten!
What's distorted about my vase's shape?
Blood Demon Art:
Ten Thousand Gliding Slime-Fish!
These 10,000 assassins
will devour you down to your bones!
And then, I'll make you one of my arts!
Mist Breathing,
Sixth Form: Lunar Dispersing Mist.
He cut them all down?
Such speed and range of attack!
Where did my poison go?
That was unexpected.
But it's no problem.
When cut by a Nichirin Sword,
my slime fish spray poison
before they turn to dust.
Moreover, the poison's toxicity is
absorbed through the skin.
Once it touches him, he'll die.
Mist Breathing, Third Form:
Scattering Mist Splash.
What!
He deflected all of it
with a rotation move!
He can even shed his skin.
What a pain.
Would you stop dodging
and climbing up trees?
I will show you my true form.
Yeah, yeah.
You're the third person I've showed it to.
Three is a lot.
Shut up!
Once I get serious, no one survives!
Very impressive.
Shut your mouth, you stupid brat!
These transparent scales are
harder and stronger than diamonds.
I refined this inside my vase.
Kneel before this perfect, beautiful form!
Say something, you dunce!
You're really getting under my scales,
damn it!
Well, you did tell me to shut my mouth.
Also,
I'm not really that impressed.
Didn't you tell me
not to climb up the trees?
Look at yourself now.
I'm only up here because you stink.
My nose can't handle it.
What do you think of my godlike hands?
Anything my fists touch
will turn into beautiful fish.
Not to mention my speed!
My body is flexible and tough!
And these scales enable me
to move quickly in any direction.
As freely as I like!
You're trembling. Are you scared?
My attacks earlier weren't even serious.
No matter how great your attacks are,
they're useless if they don't hit.
Remember that boiling rage.
I saw maggots crawling over
my beloved brother as his body rotted.
They even got into my body.
I was on the brink of death.
Prepare the hot water, hurry!
Cover his wounds with clean cloth!
Understood.
How is the older brother?
He's already drawn his last breath.
We can't afford to let the younger die.
Understood.
Big brother…
If I hadn't been lucky enough
to be rescued,
I would have died soon after.
Sir Tokito, you haven't fully healed yet.
Even if I lose my memory,
my body remembers.
The rage that won't leave me until I die.
It's the reason I trained so hard
that I vomited blood.
To destroy demons.
To eradicate all of them.
Behold my splendor as I get serious!
Blood Demon Art: Killer Fish Scales!
How do you like these moves
that defy the laws of nature?
I can move freely because of my scales!
It's impossible to predict!
I love defying the laws of nature!
Now, how should I cook your body?
I'll rip off your ugly head and replace it
with a beautiful fish head instead!
This is the end.
Mist Breathing, Seventh Form:
Obscuring Clouds.
No, over there!
I've got you!
He's gone?
Over there!
Too late!
What…
How did he disappear?
What's going on here?
Where did he go?
It's as if…
he's shrouded in mist.
Let me ask you.
Why did you think…
you were the only one who
wasn't being serious before?
What? Everything's upside down.
What's happening? My senses are gone!
That brat finally showed himself!
I have to kill him fast
and report this to Lord Muzan!
He cut it off!
He cut off my head!
It's impossible! I don't believe it!
What an extraordinary situation!
I lost?
My illustrious self lost to a child?
This is your end. Goodbye.
Don't ever be reborn again.
Shit! This shouldn't be happening!
I, Gyokko, losing my head to a mere human?
How dare you!
You're a miserable lower lifeform!
I am worth a hundred of you!
I am the superior, chosen being!
You're weak and only get old!
It's thanks to my hands, my godlike hands…
DESTROYER OF DEMONS
…that your ridiculous, worthless lives
are turned into magnificent art!
You lowly worms--
That's enough.
Just go to hell already.
DEMON SLAYER: SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
You should be open-minded
and flexible when you think, Muichiro.
When you regain your true self,
you will become stronger.
Just as the Master said.
As long as I have my true self,
I can stand on both feet
with my full strength.
Once I know who I really am,
the hesitation, confusion,
and frustration will all disappear.
No demon will be able to escape my blade.
Sir Tokito…
Sir Tokito!
Sir Tokito, thank goodness!
Are you all right?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I feel great right now.
I have to hurry to Tanjiro and his sister.
You look extremely pale.
Are you really sure you're okay?
I'm totally fine.
Didn't you hear me?
You're huffing and puffing, sir.
And your body is trembling, isn't it?
-I'm fine, so…
-Sir, hang on!
Would you please go to Kotetsu--
You're foaming at the mouth!
Sir Tokito!
This is bad! Is he going to die?
What should I do? Someone, help!
Haganezuka!
That bastard isn't coming!
Even when I was about to be killed,
he completely ignored it!
He's choking on the foam!
What should I do?
You should turn him on his side.
Okay.
It's young Kotetsu's ghost!
No, I'm not dead at all,
so I'm not a ghost.
No, no! Ghosts don't know
that they're already dead!
No, no. Look, I'm still alive.
No, no! There's no way you're still alive
bleeding so much from your stomach!
This blood is from my wounded arm.
I was holding it and it got stuck.
The wound is pretty deep,
so I might die if it doesn't stop.
As for my stomach…
I was saved by this sword guard
that Tanjiro entrusted to me.
He said he wanted to put it
on his new sword.
Let's do our best together as Hashira!
See?
It all worked out.
Father…
Mother…
Muichiro.
You did well.
Big brother…
Thank you.
There are five tree dragon heads.
They can stretch about 66 shaku.
Okay, I figured one thing out.
HATE
Hinokami Kagura: Clear Blue--
My… My eardrums burst.
I'm dizzy. I can't get up.
This is bad. Hurry, stand up! Quick!
The attack is coming!
He can also use
the four emotion demons' abilities.
And the power is increasing.
I don't have time to breathe.
I can't recover.
Even if I know when an attack is coming,
I'm no longer able to counter.
I can't keep breathing.
But I'll manage
if I can get 66 shaku away.
Okay, I should be good here.
Use a technique!
Slash it!
UPPER - FOUR
It's no use. I'll get crushed…
This is the end for you.
A Hashira?
What a monster! What is that?
Miss Kanroji!
Are you okay? Sorry, I'm late.
You were in quite a pinch.
Miss Kanroji!
Tanjiro.
You can rest now!
You did well! Good job!
I can't hear what she's saying
with these burst eardrums.
Tanjiro.
I'll save Nezuko and Genya.
Little girl…
Leave the rest to me!
Wait!
It's an Upper Rank! Upper Rank Four!
DEMON SLAYER: SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
NO. 9
What about our screen time?
Hey, when do I go out?
I don't sense the enemy at all.
Where's the enemy?
I said we don't get any screen time!
Then we'll finish our mission
and go on to the next one.
Next up, Episode 10:
"Love Hashira Mitsuri Kanroji."
Beat that Upper Rank!
You understand, Senbachiro?
TO BE CONTINUED